=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 4=
= الحلقة 4 =
Hello, dear.
مرحباً عزيزي.
Are you at the hospital now?
هل انت في المستشفى الان؟
(Hello, Mr. Jiang.)
(مرحبا السيد جيانغ.)
(I'm Dr. Xu.)
(أنا دكتور شو.)
(Ms. Xiang steps out to get her medical report.)
(تخرج السيدة شيانغ للحصول على تقرير طبي لها).
(She'll be back soon.)
(ستعود قريبًا.)
Oh.
أوه.
It's you, Dr. Xu.
أنت يا دكتور شو.
I'd like to know
أود أن أعرف
about the result of the test.
حول نتيجة الاختبار.
No worries.
لا داعى للقلق.
The result is normal.
النتيجة طبيعية.
By the way, Mr. Jiang.
بالمناسبة ، السيد جيانغ.
(The medicine for soothing emotions you requested)
(الدواء الذي طلبته لتهدئة المشاعر)
(is sent to you.)
(يتم إرسالها إليك.)
I see.
أرى.
Thank you so much.
شكرا جزيلا لك.
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
(You should come for the screening test too.)
(يجب أن تحضر لاختبار الفحص أيضًا.)
Well.
نحن سوف.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'm quite tied up lately.
أنا مقيد تمامًا مؤخرًا.
Maybe next week.
ربما الأسبوع القادم.
I'll arrange my time.
سأرتب وقتي.
(Do take care of your health.)
(اعتني بصحتك.)
Take less alcohol
تناول كمية أقل من الكحول
and sleep early.
والنوم مبكرا.
Something you ask for will happen.
شيء تطلبه سيحدث.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Well.
نحن سوف.
See you around.
أراك بالجوار.
(Sure.)
(بالتأكيد.)
Naughty.
شقي.
Do you miss me already?
هل اشتقت لي بالفعل؟
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
What a smooth talker.
يا له من حديث سلس.
I rushed hotfoot from the airport.
هرعت هوت فوت من المطار.
Carry me in.
احملني.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Yes?
نعم؟
It'd be great if you're the first person I see
سيكون من الرائع أن تكون أول شخص أراه
when I wake up every morning.
عندما أستيقظ كل صباح.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Yes?
نعم؟
Do I get in the way of you and Wei?
هل أعترض طريقك أنت ووي؟
I should keep my feelings for you inside
يجب أن أحتفظ بمشاعري في داخلك
and I don't wish that it would disturb you.
ولا أتمنى أن يزعجك ذلك.
Who's the little sexy
من هو القليل المثير
bewitching my heart?
يسحر قلبي؟
Who's that little sexy?
من هو هذا مثير قليلا؟
Do you know who's it?
هل تعرف من هو؟
Do you know it now?
هل تعرفه الآن؟
Stop playing.
وقف اللعب.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Hey.
يا.
I have something serious to tell you.
لدي شيء جاد لأخبرك به.
What's it?
ما هذا؟
Can you stay with me tonight?
هل يمكنك البقاء معي الليلة؟
I'm afraid of staying here alone.
أخشى البقاء هنا وحدي.
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Didn't I tell you
ألم أخبرك
everything'll be fine soon
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام قريبا
if you wait for a while more?
إذا انتظرت بعض الوقت أكثر؟
Then,
ثم،
when
متى
are you...
أنت...
Erm...
ERM ...
Regarding the divorce,
وأما الطلاق ،
I'll deal with it some other time.
سوف أتعامل معها في وقت آخر.
I found something's wrong with her lately.
لقد وجدت شيئًا ما خطأ معها مؤخرًا.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Yes?
نعم؟
I want to be the supportive woman
أريد أن أكون المرأة الداعمة
behind you for good.
خلفك للخير.
You're so precious.
أنت غالي جدًا.
I need to go back now.
أنا بحاجة للعودة الآن.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Mom.
أم.
Dear.
عزيزي.
Surprise!
مفاجئة!
Happy Chinese Valentine's Day.
عيد حب صيني سعيد.
Dear.
عزيزي.
Huh?
هاه؟
I thought you were supposed to fly back tomorrow.
اعتقدت أنه كان من المفترض أن تعود غدا.
Why did you come back early?
لماذا عدت مبكرا؟
How could I bear to leave you alone
كيف يمكنني أن أتحمل أن أتركك وشأنك
on this important day?
في هذا اليوم المهم؟
I must spend the night with you.
يجب أن أقضي الليلة معك.
You're so kind to me, dear.
أنت لطيف معي يا عزيزتي.
By the way,
على فكرة،
Zijie took your bag
أخذ Zijie حقيبتك
two days ago.
قبل يومين.
Yes.
نعم.
I've ordered
لقد طلبت
a limited edition online.
طبعة محدودة على الإنترنت.
It'll arrive a few days later.
ستصل بعد أيام قليلة.
Dear.
عزيزي.
You must be tired.
يجب أن تكون متعبا.
I'll make you some food.
سأعد لك بعض الطعام.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
(The medical report is here.)
(التقرير الطبي هنا).
(The medical report)
(التقرير الطبي)
(Weiwei did go to the hospital today.)
(ذهب ويوي إلى المستشفى اليوم).
(Perhaps I've overthought.)
(ربما كنت قد بالغت في التفكير.)
Dear.
عزيزي.
What did you cook?
ماذا طبخت؟
Did you ask Dr. Xu to prescribe some medicine?
هل طلبت من دكتور شو أن يصف لك بعض الأدوية؟
Yes.
نعم.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
I'll take the medicine with you.
سآخذ الدواء معك.
We'll encounter the bitterness together.
سنواجه المرارة معا.
Dear.
عزيزي.
How considerate of you.
كيف مراعي لك.
Come on.
تعال.
Cheers.
هتافات.
What's wrong, Dad and Mom?
ما بك أبي وأمي؟
Why did you ask me back
لماذا طلبت مني العودة
on short notice?
في وقت قصير؟
Good news.
أخبار جيدة.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
After a discussion with your dad,
بعد مناقشة مع والدك ،
we decided to have you return to Xiang Group
قررنا أن تعود إلى Xiang Group
and also offer you a three per cent share.
ونقدم لك أيضًا حصة بنسبة 3 في المائة.
But,
لكن،
I thought Wei is the rightful successor of Xiang Group.
اعتقدت أن Wei هو الخليفة الشرعي لمجموعة Xiang Group.
It's inappropriate for me to take the share.
من غير المناسب بالنسبة لي أن آخذ الحصة.
Wei has been keeping her nose out of the family over these years.
دأبت وي على إبقاء أنفها بعيدًا عن العائلة على مدار هذه السنوات.
She's in no place
إنها ليست في مكان
to point the finger at us.
لتوجيه أصابع الاتهام إلينا.
But,
لكن،
I'm scared
أنا خائف
that I'm not capable enough
أنني لست قادرًا بما فيه الكفاية
and let you down.
وخذلك.
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
Your dad's blood
دم والدك
is in Wei's and your veins.
موجود في وي وفي عروقك.
You'll do better than Wei
ستفعل أفضل من وي
in the things she's capable of.
في الأشياء التي تستطيع القيام بها.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Both Weiwei and you are my daughters.
كلاكما ويوي وأنت ابنتاي.
I won't be stingy
لن أكون بخيل
about what you're supposed to own.
حول ما يفترض أن تمتلكه.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Yes.
نعم.
There is something
يوجد شيء
you need to grip in your hand
تحتاج إلى الإمساك بيدك
to make you feel secure.
لتجعلك تشعر بالأمان.
I'll make you own
سأجعلك تملك
the entire Xiang Group one day.
مجموعة شيانغ بأكملها في يوم من الأيام.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
(Cici)
(سيسي)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
(Mr. Jiang.)
(السيد جيانغ.)
(Something bad has happened.)
(حدث شيء سيء).
(Several customers)
(عدة عملاء)
(have developed severe skin allergies)
(أصيبوا بحساسية جلدية شديدة)
(after using our product.)
(بعد استخدام منتجنا.)
(This incident grabs the headlines today.)
(يحتل هذا الحادث عناوين الصحف اليوم).
(Just now, Ruide Group)
(الآن ، مجموعة Ruide)
(sent us an email to pull out before the company goes public.)
(أرسل إلينا بريدًا إلكترونيًا لسحبها قبل أن تصبح الشركة عامة.)
I'll come right now.
سآتي الآن.
Gather everyone for the meeting.
اجمع الجميع للاجتماع.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Make an appointment
إحجز موعد
with Mr. Gu of Ruide for a dinner tonight.
مع السيد Gu of Ruide لتناول العشاء الليلة.
(All right. I'll arrange it now.)
(حسنًا ، سأرتبها الآن.)
Spicy meat dumplings?
فطائر اللحم الحار؟
Dear.
عزيزي.
Didn't you forbid me to eat spicy food in the morning
ألم تمنعني من تناول الطعام الحار في الصباح
because of my weak stomach?
بسبب معدتي الضعيفة؟
Even if I'd forbidden you to eat it,
حتى لو منعتك من أكله ،
didn't you have a bite on the side?
ألم يكن لديك لدغة على الجانب؟
♪If you insist on leaving, I'll let you go♪
♪ إذا أصررت على المغادرة ، فسأطلق سراحك ♪
♪My love for you, I'll keep it♪
♪ حبي لك ، سأحتفظ به ♪
♪Encountering you in a different world♪
♪ مواجهتك في عالم مختلف ♪
♪I'm content♪
♪ أنا راضٍ ♪
♪With what I possessed before♪
بما كنت أملكه من قبل ♪
♪An unexpected love♪
♪ حب غير متوقع ♪
♪Is an abrupt blessing♪
هي نعمة فجائية
♪Regardless of whether your love is genuine or not♪
♪ بغض النظر عما إذا كان حبك حقيقي أم لا
♪Your place in my heart never changes♪
مكانتك في قلبي لا تتغير
♪Even if I have to be punished for falling for you♪
♪ حتى لو كان يجب أن أعاقب لوقوعك في حبك ♪
♪I'm not afraid of that♪
♪ لست خائفًا من ذلك ♪
♪Bring it on. I won't back down♪
اجلبه.  لن أتراجع ♪